directtoolsoutlet.com 2017-06-06

# Direct Tools | Privacy Policy

Techtronic Industries Factory Outlets, Inc. d/b/a Direct Tools Factory Outlet ("we", "us", "our", or "Direct Tools") created this Web Site Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to ensure the confidence of visitors and customers ("you" or "your") of and to our Web site, directtoolsoutlet.com (the "Site"), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy, including compliance with California Privacy Rights. This Privacy Policy does not apply to collection of data from sources other than the Site.

1\. Types of Information Collected   
a. Traffic Data Collected. We automatically track and collect the following information when you visit our Site, including your: (i) IP address; (ii) domain server; (iii) type of computer; (iv) type of web browser; and (v) other logs (collectively "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. We also use "cookies" to customize content specific to your interests and to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site.   
b. Personal Information Collected. In order for you to access certain services and to purchase products that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Personal Information may include: (i) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing and e-mail addresses) and (ii) Demographic Data (such as your city, state, zip code, area code, gender, and age). If you communicate with us by e-mail, posting messages to our Site, or otherwise completing online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

2\. Uses of Information Collected   
We use Contact Data and/or Demographic Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or to contact you when necessary. We will direct electronic communications to your email address. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Site and to assist us in product development and marketing. We do not share your Personal Information with outside parties.  We may share your Personal Information with third parties as required for them to provide services to us, such as hosting services, marketing services, and warranty services.

3\. Sharing of Personal Information   
We do not share Demographic Data with other third parties. We do not share Contact Data with other companies, other than subsidiaries of Techtronic Industries Factory Outlets, Inc., or One World Technologies, Inc.

4\. User Choice Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of Personal Information   
You must provide us with your Contact Data in order to set up an account on the site. If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from Direct Tools, you may select the appropriate "opt-out" option in the account set-up portion. 

5\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information   
Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to:   
(a) comply with a court order or other legal process;   
(b) protect our rights or property; or   
(c) enforce any terms of use associated with this Site. We take security measures that we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, but given the nature of the Internet, we cannot guaranty the security of the information. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers that are not legitimately accessible by third parties, except for our third party agents providing the services associated with this Site.

6\. User Ability to Access, Update and Correct Personal Information   
In order to ensure that all of your Contact Information is correct and up-to-date, at any time you may visit the Site, log in and select the "My Account" option. Through your personal profile you may review and update your Contact Information that we have already collected.   

7\. Other Limits to Your Privacy   
The Site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

8\. Children's Privacy   
Directtoolsoutlet.com is considered to be general audience site and is not to be used by children. Direct Tools does not sell products that are intended for children and does not intend to collect Personal Information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18). If you are the parent or guardian of a child who has provided personal information to us, please inform us as provided under Section 13 below, and we will delete that Personal Information. 

9\. Business Transition    
In the event our company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

10\. Your California Privacy Rights    
Residents of the State of California, under certain provisions of the California Civil Code, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed certain personally identifiable information as defined under California law during the preceding year for third party direct marketing purposes. You are limited to one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. You may request the information in writing at: 

Techtronic Industries Factory Outlets, Inc.  
Attention: Customer Service  
1428 Pearman Dairy Road  
Anderson, South Carolina 29625

11\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy   
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. Therefore, it is important that you periodically review this Privacy Policy.

12\. Further Information   
If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us as follows:   
Customer Service:  1-800-323-4615 

Address:  
Techtronic Industries Factory Outlets, Inc.  
1428 Pearman Dairy Road  
Anderson, South Carolina 29625

Any questions, comments or concerns "specifically" about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [privacy@directtoolsoutlet.com.](mailto:privacy@directtoolsoutlet.com)
